The answer is android.permission.INTERNET. I'll show you now,
where it's located in the code. Under the
main folder open up the Android manifest.xml file.
Within the Android manifest file, we declare uses
permission, with the name of the permission. We
verified that the data returned is correct by
adding a verbose log statement for printing out
the forecastJsonStr. This is in the fetch weather task.
We can verify that it's going to show up in the logs. For this example, I'm
going to use the command line. These are the real time logs, and then if I
hit refresh, then I see the weather data here. The verbose log, and this is our
log tag fetch weather task. Here's the forecastJsonStr,
and this is all the output from the server.